cupshe.com 2019-05-30

# Cupshe - Live Life On The Beach

**_**_SECTION 1 - INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU_**_**

  * ********Information Provided by You Upon Registration  or Making a Purchase Online or at Our Stores. ****We may use this Personal Information to administer your access to a Site, verify your identity, and provide our products or services to you.
  * ********Information Provided When You Contact Us.  ****We may use this Personal Information to understand and respond to your question or comment.
  * ********General Uses.  ****We may also use your Personal Information to improve and personalize your experience with us, and, with your consent where necessary, send you information about us and keep you informed of our other products and services that may be of interest to you.
  * ********Passively Collected Information.  ****We use passively collected information to monitor and maintain the performance of our Sites, analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our services, validate users and ensure their technological compatibility with users, and optimize our marketing efforts.
  * ********Aggregate data.  ****We may use your Personal Information to create aggregate data which does not include any Personal Information and which cannot be used to identify you. For example, aggregate data may include data that describes the general demographics, usage or other characteristics of a Site's users. We reserve the right to transfer and/or sell aggregate or group data about a Site's users for lawful purposes.
  * ********Email marketing (if applicable).**** With your permission, we may send you emails about our store, new products and other updates.

**_**_SECTION 2 - CONSENT_**_**

  * ********How do you get my consent?****  
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, verify your credit card, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only.  
If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
  * ********How do I withdraw my consent?****  
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at service@cupshe.zendesk.com. 

**_**_SECTION 3 - DISCLOSURE_**_** ** _ ** __**_** ** _ ** __**_**

We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.

**_**_SECTION 4 - SHOPIFY_**_**

**_**__**_**Our store is hosted on Shopify Inc. They provide us with the online e-commerce platform that allows us to sell our products and services to you.  
Your data is stored through Shopify’s data storage, databases and the general Shopify application. They store your data on a secure server behind a firewall.

 ** **Payment:****  
If you choose a direct payment gateway to complete your purchase, then Shopify stores your credit card data. It is encrypted through the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS). Your purchase transaction data is stored only as long as is necessary to complete your purchase transaction. After that is complete, your purchase transaction information is deleted.  
All direct payment gateways adhere to the standards set by PCI-DSS as managed by the PCI Security Standards Council, which is a joint effort of brands like Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover.  
PCI-DSS requirements help ensure the secure handling of credit card information by our store and its service providers.  
For more insight, you may also want to read Shopify’s Terms of Service (https://www.shopify.com/legal/terms) or Privacy Statement (https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

 ** _ ** _S_**_** ** _ ** _ECTION 5 -_**_** ** _ ** _THIRD-PARTY SERVICES_**_**

In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.  
However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions.  
For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers.  
In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located a different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.  
As an example, if you are located in Canada and your transaction is processed by a payment gateway located in the United States, then your personal information used in completing that transaction may be subject to disclosure under United States legislation, including the Patriot Act.  
Once you leave our store’s website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website’s Terms of Service.

 ** **Links to Other Websites**** ** **.**** When you click on links on our store, they may direct you away from our site. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We suggest that you contact these third parties directly for information regarding their privacy, security and data collection and distribution policies prior to providing them with any information.

****Google analytics**** ** **.**** To help facilitate the delivery of relevant content, we use Google Analytics and have implemented the following Google Advertising Features: Remarketing, Impression Reporting, and Demographics and Interest Reporting. We use Google Analytics cookies and other Google advertising cookies. You can opt out of the Google Analytics Advertising Features we use by indicating your preference using the interest-based opt-out link here. Google also provides a complete privacy policy, and instructions on opting out of Google Analytics here. Note that Google's opt-out mechanism is specific to Google activities and does not affect the activities of other ad networks or analytics providers that we may use.

 ** _ ** _SECTION 6 - SECURITY_**_**

**_**__**_**To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.  
If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with a AES-256 encryption. Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

 ** _ ** _  
_**_** ** _ ** _SECTION 7 - COOKIES_**_**

**_**__**_**Here is a list of cookies that we use. We’ve listed them here so you that you can choose if you want to opt-out of cookies or not.

  * ****_session_id**** , unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).
  * ****_**** ** **shopify_visit**** , no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, Used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits.
  * ****_shopify_uniq**** , no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.
  * cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.
  * ****_secure_session_id**** , unique token, sessional.
  * ****storefront_digest**** , unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

The way we use: 

\- Instructions on how to opt out of receiving targeted advertising or may have Opt-out link.  
\- The advertiser needs to include opt-out information or link in the privacy policy section in order to toggle privacy policy to yes.

PREF, persistent for a very short period, Set by Google and tracks who visits the store and from where.

 ** _ ** _SECTION 8 - AGE OF CONSENT_**_** ** _ ** __**_**

**_**__**_**Visitors under 13 years of age are not permitted to use and/or submit their Personal Information at any Site. We do not knowingly solicit or collect information from visitors under 13 years of age. If you are under 13 years of age, please do not submit any information to us. In the event that we learn that a person under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such personal information. Visitors older than the age of 13, but younger than their country's legal age of majority are permitted to use and/or submit their Personal Information only with parental supervision. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.

 ** _ ** _SECTION 9 - CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY_**_** ** _ ** __**_**

**_**__**_**We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here that it has been updated, so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we use and/or disclose it.  
If our store is acquired or merged with another company, your information may be transferred to the new owners so that we may continue to sell products to you.

**_**_QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION_**_** ** _ ** __**_**

**_**__**_**If you would like to: access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact our Privacy Compliance Officer at legal@cupshe.com
